麦克斯 成啦
This is it, Max.
这是我们小店接的第一个私人派对单呢
The first private party we've booked in our cupcake shop.
干嘛 你说私人派对啊
What? You said it was a private party,
这是我放在"私"处旁的"派对"
And this is a party I keep near my privates.
随你吧 不过不能让人家闻到酒味
Fine, but they can't smell it on your breath,
等会吃颗薄荷糖吧
So eat a mint after.
不必 这刚好是薄荷杜松子酒
No need. It's peppermint schnapps,
看我多深谋远虑啊
'cause I think ahead.
这值得来一段"首次派对"舞吧
I think this calls for a "first party" dance.
* 首次派对 *
* First par-tay *
* 谁首次要派对啦 *
* Who gonna have a first par-tay *
* 我们首次要派对啦 *
* We gon' have a first par-tay *
保护动物协会上次送你
That's the exact same dance you did
狗狗地址条的时候 你不也跳这支舞吗
when the humane society sent you free puppy address labels.
* 地址条 *
* Address labels *
* 谁家信封上有狗狗地址条啊 *
* Who got doggies on an envelope *
* 我得再喝一口啦 *
* I need another sip of this *
* 真希望我有更烈的酒 *
* Wish I had something stronger *
麦克斯 不好意思啦 我忍不住嘛
Max, I'm sorry. I can't help it.
想到我天才般的营销策略终于有成效
I'm just so excited my genius marketing ideas
我就兴奋得不得了嘛
are finally starting to pay off.
安静 安静
Quiet! Quiet!
安静 都安静
你们不好好听话
If you aren't listening,
小蛋糕麦克斯姐姐怎么教你们弄装饰啊
Cupcake Max can't teach you how to decorate.
性爱如此愉悦
It's weird how sex is so great,
为何后果令人想哭
and yet, it makes these.
呵 呵 呵
Ho ho ho!
在跟你说呢 麦克斯
Talking to you, Max.
我知道 怎么样 安迪
I know. What's up, Andy?
像圣诞老人一样带糖果来送你们啦
I brought some christmas candy from my shop for the diner.
麦克斯 圣诞老人真的来了[高潮]
Look, Max, Santa did come.
亲个嘴就高潮啊
From just a kiss?
那是你没看到她的手在底下干嘛了
Well, you didn't see what she was doing with her hands.
那是我教她的
I taught her that.
算我给你的礼物 圣诞快乐啦
That's my gift to you. Merry christmas.
对了 你们的小店都还好吧
Hey, is everything okay with your shop?
今天你们房东走进我的店
'Cause the landlord came into my store today
说你们还没付租金呢
and mentioned you guys hadn't paid your rent.
要是有什么问题 我很乐意帮忙啊
If there's a problem, I'd be more than happy to help.
其实呢 我们不够...
Well, the fact is, we just don't have--
我们完全不知道我们的线上转账
Don't have a clue why our online payments
怎么没入到他账呢 科技真不靠谱啊
just never go through. Technology, right?
想当年我们还能跟邮差先生握握手
You used to be able to shake the mailman's hand.
现在就剩全息影像跟激光了
Now it's all holograms and lasers.
老奶奶说得对 当年的确是那样
Grandma's right, those were the days.
想当年 人们多诚实啊
It was a more honest time.
好啦 我得走了
Okay. Well, I gotta go.
送卡洛琳宝贝一个吻
A kiss for Caroline.
哎哟 新吻法耶
Oh, that was a new kind of kiss.
我喜欢
I liked it.
麦克斯教我的
Max taught me.
你干嘛要撒谎 跟他坦白不行吗
What's with the lies? Just tell him the truth.
我们付不出租金 生活惨惨戚戚
We can't pay our rent, life sucks,
要你口交得先灌醉你
and you need wine before oral.
不用跟他说
No need.
我们这个月还有两个私人派对单呢
We still have two other private parties set up for this month:
那个怀胎少女的成年礼
the quinceanera for that pregnant girl,
与之后她宝宝的迎婴派对
and then her baby shower.
而且圣诞节也要到了
Plus, the holidays are coming,
我们也该尽快弄好把圣诞装饰
So we should get our decorations up ASAP,
不然圣诞老公公会找不到我们哦
or Santa won't know where to find us.
他才不会找不到呢
Oh, he'll know where to find us.
我们会是两个被人赶出门
We'll be the two evicted girls
从垃圾堆里找食物的悲催女
eating fruitcake out of a dumpster.
你看 圣诞老人的其中一只麋鹿来了
Oh, look, here comes one of the reindeers now.
你看起来像个韩国衣帽架
You look like a Korean coat rack.
大家不用费心找了
Everybody can stop looking.
怪物圣诞怪杰就在这
We found the grinch.
也难怪她易怒 领着最低工资能不易怒吗
No wonder it's so angry, it's working for minimum wage.
你在挂圣诞装饰啊
Oh, you're hanging the Christmas decorations.
我已经把榭寄生挂好了呢
I already put up the mistletoe.
你挂哪了
Where?
反正挂得非常好[非常大雕]就是了
Let's just say it's very well-hung.
我的单都交上去了
Well, all my checks are in,
所以我要去外送小蛋糕了
so I have to run and make a cupcake delivery.
给 把这些放进小店里的收银机吧
Here, take this and put it in the till.
我昨晚也去外送了
I did a cupcake run last night too.
等等 有谁会半夜两点叫小蛋糕啊
Wait, who orders cupcakes at 2:00 A.M.?
就我的一些朋友啊
Um, my friends.
你又没有朋友
You don't have any friends.
我朋友超多好吗
I have so many friends.
你朋友都谁啊
Who are your friends?
就我认识的一些人啊
Some people I know.
那我怎么都没见过呢
Then how come I've never met them?
因为他们不喜欢你
Well, they don't like you.
他们又不认识我
But they don't know me.
他们听过你的事迹之后不喜欢你
They don't like what they've heard about you.
他们能知道也都是你说出来的事吧
But who would they have heard things from but you?
也可以是从我别群朋友那里听的啊
Maybe from my other group of friends.
他们也不喜欢你 再见啦
They don't like you either. Later.
麦克斯 转过身来
Max, you can turn around.
没错 我跟踪了你
That's right, I followed you.
抱歉我跟踪了你
Sorry for following you.
只是你跟一个女人的发型和外套很像
It's just, you have the hair and jacket of a woman.
我是称赞你啦
In a good way.
你不会把他认错成是我吧
Did you actually think that was me?
我的胡须比他浓密多了
My beard is much thicker.
我们到底是要上哪去啊
Well, where are we going?
我们干嘛来这个破烂建筑里啊
Why are we in this seedy building
这里好浓的大麻味
That smells like marijuana?
天啊 这里是你妈妈住的地方吗
Oh, my God, is this where your mom lives?
你居然以为我妈住室内啊
You think my mom lives indoors?
好啦 最近几晚
Okay, look, for the last few nights,
我的大麻贩友人在卖货后会通知我
my dealer calls me after she sells pot to people,
然后我就趁人抽完肚子饿时来卖零嘴
and then I sell those people the munchies they need.
麦克斯 这里是纽约 那是犯法的
Max, this is New York. That's illegal!
才没有 大瓶汽水才犯法呢
No, giant sodas are illegal.
我这是在卖小蛋糕赚租金
This is me selling cupcakes to make our rent.
而且这又没什么大不了的
And besides, it's not a big deal.
在华盛顿州 麻省 科罗拉多州 加州
Pot's legal in Washington, Massachusetts,
大麻可都是合法的呢
Colorado, and California.
感谢你的选举过后 毒虫政策精选啊
Well, thank you for the stoner's summary of the last election,
但我们又不住那些地方
but we don't live in any of those places,
而我也完全讨厌大麻这玩意
And I do not approve of pot at all.
让人们懒惰又恍惚
It makes people lazy and lethargic,
还把人的理想志向全吸走
and drains all one's ambitions.
天啊 你真"有趣"
God, you're fun.
在这扇门的背后
Look, on the other side of this door
有着能让我们多付600块租金的机会
is money to help us make the $600 more we need for rent.
你决定吧
It's totally up to you.
我该敲门 还是不敲门呢
Should I knock, or not knock?
你好吗 麦克斯
What's good, Max?
琦芙 她是我的朋友 卡洛琳
Hey, Keefer. This is my friend Caroline.
幸会 美丽的女神
Pleasure, my goddess.
进来吧 我刚开了一些高纯麻[鸡块]抽呢
Come on in. I just broke out some dank nugs.
谢了 我们才刚吃过不久呢
Oh, thanks, but we actually just had some dank nugs.
以后这就是你的绰号了
First of all, that's your new nickname,
还有 琦芙 我不想催你
And, Keefer, I don't want to rush you,
但是我跟鸡块妹赶着回家
but me and dank nugs have to get home.
行 没问题 我马上拿钱过来
Okay, cool, I'll be right back with the cash.
二手烟 二手烟
Second-hand smoke, second-hand smoke.
二手弱宅 二手弱宅
Second-hand nerd, second-hand nerd.
拿去吧
Here you go,
他们今晚挺大方的
they were feeling kinda generous.
很高兴见到你啊 鸡块妹
Nice to meet you, nugs.
我也很高兴认识你啊
Nice meeting you too.
再见啦
Peace.
一看 整整一百块
There. A hundred bucks.
天啊 麦克斯 百元大钞呢
Oh, my God, Max, that's a hundred-dollar bill!
你看 多轻松啊
How easy was that?
而且连店面都不需要
And we didn't even have to open the shop.
我这样卖哪有什么不行嘛
I mean, what is the problem with doing this?
你说得对 我反应过激了
You're right, I overreacted.
我们又不是卖大麻 只是卖小蛋糕而已
We're not selling pot. We're selling cupcakes.
我们又没犯法
We didn't break any laws.
完全没有不法之处
There's nothing illegal about it.
闪边 闪边 闪边
Move! Move! Move!
我不知道 我真不知情啊
I didn't know! I didn't know!
上上上 快上啊
Go! Go! Go! Keep going, now!
警察 上啊 快上
Police! Go! Go, now!
放下你手中的冰毒 快放下你的冰毒
Put the meth down! Put the meth down!
你好啊 帅哥
'Sup?
走 出来吧 把他揪出来
Move! Go! Go! Get him out! Let's go!
快把他给揪出来 出来 出来
Bring him out! Go! Go! Go!
我都说了让你别跟毒品沾边
I told you not to get involved with drugs!
我早告诉过你了
I told you!
闭嘴 卡洛 闭嘴
Shut it, Carol! Shut it!
我真不敢相信刚才那一切
I can't believe that just happened.
对啊 感觉就是"少废话了 卡洛"
I know, it's like, "let it go, Carol."
我们不许再跟毒沾边了 我没说错
We're done with drugs. I was right.
现在知道为什么我的朋友们都讨厌你了吧
And now you know why my friends don't like you.
别忘了 我们也接私人派对
And remember, we do private parties,
婚礼派对 生日派对....
Wedding parties, birthday parties--
好了 一打小蛋糕 庆祝什么呢
All right, there's a dozen. What's the special occasion?
我的猫死掉了
My cat died.
我们也接丧礼 离婚...
we also do funerals, divorces...
孤单周五晚的单也接
and sad friday nights alone.
谢谢惠顾
Thank you.
好了 又赚了48块钱
Okay, so that's 48 more dollars.
-我们只需要... -再有72只猫死就行了
- Now, all we need is - For 72 more cats to die.
麦克斯 别这样乱咒猫嘛
Max, there's no need to kill imaginary cats.
我们只需多发送正面能量
Let's just send out positive energy,
老天爷就会安排好的
and the universe will provide.
失手了啊 老天爷
Swing and a miss, universe.
给你们惊喜 我刚好来附近
Surprise! I was in the neighborhood
就想着过来打声招呼
and thought I'd stop by and say hello.
平常呢 我会说"不准你再不请自来"
Under any other circumstance, I'd say, "never do that again,"
但今天特别 所以"你要买多少小蛋糕呢"
But today, I'm saying, "how many cupcakes do you want""
我觉得就来个10到20个吧
And I'm thinking of a number between 10 and 20.
我想看着我的腰[照顾体重]呢
I'm kind of trying to watch my waist.
你的头已经比别人更近腰了
Well, you're closer to it than most people.
就先给你来个12个小蛋糕吧
I'm gonna start you with 12 cupcakes.
你算家人 就"原价"招待吧
Full price, 'cause you're family.
天啊 一边有顾客上门
Oh, my God! The phone ringing
一边还有顾客打来
and a customer at the same time?
麦克斯 我们的好运到啦
See, Max, it's all happening.
我们昨晚赚到的钱
Between the money we just got last night
加怀胎少女的成年礼与迎婴派对
and that pregnant girl's Quinceanera / Baby shower,
绝对能赚到租金啊
we're gonna make our rent.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕
Max's Homemade Cupcakes.
你好啊 埃斯特拉[西语]
Oh, hola, Estella.
是的 成年礼加迎婴派对
Si, the Quinceanera / Baby shower.
怎么了
Que?
不是吧 遣返
Oh, no. Deported?
哦 是付不起啊
Oh, you can't afford it.
我听错了
My mal.
很遗憾未能为你服务 感谢来电
Well, sorry, it didn't work out. Gracias for calling.
这下失望了吧
Well, that's disappointing,
不过我们早该料到有这下场
but we should have seen it coming.
她连避孕套都买不起
She couldn't afford condoms either.
没事
It's cool.
我再打给琦芙吧
I'll just call Keefer
帮她多外送几趟就行了
and try to do a couple more cupcake runs.
不许这样 这太冒险了
No, that's not cool, that's dangerous.
船到桥头自然直 这样吧
It'll all work out. You know what?
我这就过去问安迪
I'm just gonna go over and ask Andy
借点钱周转 节日高峰期过后就能还他了
if he'll float us some cash till the holiday rush kicks in.
他也说过要借啊
He did offer.
我们也应该挂上圣诞灯
We should put up some Christmas lights,
犹太光明节的烛台 以及宽扎节的...
a menorah for Chanukah, and for Kwanzaa...
我去的时候 你搜搜宽扎节摆饰吧
While I'm gone, why don't you Wikipedia Kwanzaa?
好了 先上八个给你
Well... Here's the first eight.
你还想外带多少个小蛋糕走呢
And how many cupcakes would you like "to go"?
我觉得就来个40到50个吧
I'm thinking of a number between 40 and 50.
你在餐馆的时候怎么不这么推销食物啊
How come you never push the food at the diner like this?
对哦 我是在那里认识你的啊
Oh, that's where I know you from.
快开吃吧
Start eating.
我没问他借
I didn't do it.
这样太不性感了 他是我男朋友呢
It's so not hot. He's my boyfriend.
没办法像跟亲人借钱那样自然
I mean, it's not like borrowing money from family.
毕竟我们又不跟自己家人"睡"
You don't sleep with your family.
有些家庭就不是这样呢 卡洛琳
Not all families are the same, Caroline.
而且 我们没事的 老天爷会照顾我们
Besides, we're fine. The universe will provide.
那老天爷最好是这几秒内
Well, the universe better provide in,
赶紧照顾我们啊 房东来了
like, a second, 'cause look, there's the landlord.
他已经到斜对面摩洛哥店了
He just went into that Moroccan place.
我们该怎么办
What are we gonna do?
-躲啊 -什么
- Hide! - What?
好了 我该走了
Well, I should go.
想走已经太迟了
It's too late for that!
锁门 关灯
Lock the door, hit the lights,
爬过来 蹲下身子
and crawl over here, and stay low!
在他看不见前 不要起身
Stay down till we're out of sight.
膝盖好疼哦
Ow, it hurts!
拜托 说得像这是
Oh, please. Like this is the first time
你第一次在厕所里"跪地抬臀"一样
you've been on your knees in the bathroom.
卡洛琳 进来就不用趴地上了啊
Caroline, you don't have to stay on the ground anymore.
我觉得我现在低等得只配趴地上
I feel like this is where I belong now.
烘焙女孩们
Yo, baker girls.
麦克斯 他进店了
Max, he's in the shop.
-好吧 爬窗吧 -你说真的吗
- Okay, go, out the window. - Really?
他要是没见到我们 就不能赶走我们
If he can't see us, he can't evict us.
快啊
Go.
有点高耶 你确定吗
It's a little high. Are you sure?
你听过"当上帝关上门 他也开一扇窗"吧
You've heard "when God closes a door, he opens a window"?
他当时就是在躲房东
He's running from his landlord.
跳吧
Go.
好吧 我跳啦
Okay, here goes.
麦克斯 我爱你
I love you, Max.
那我呢 我怎么办
What about me? What should I do?
把小蛋糕的钱放柜台上
Put the money for those cupcakes on the counter.
你是谁啊
Who are you?
"偶不东英文"
No hablo ingles?
好了 好消息
All right, all right, good news.
我刚在我口袋发现3块钱
I just found $3 in my pocket.
还有一颗M&M花生巧克力豆
Oh, and a peanut M&M,
我们今晚不必花钱吃晚餐啦
so we don't have to spend money on dinner.
卡洛琳 别再闪躲了
Caroline, why are you putting it off?
该干嘛你自己知道
You know what you have to do.
乖乖伸手去掏沙发缝吧
Go over to the couch and put your hands in that crack.
每个穷姑娘都躲不过这件事
It's every poor girl's rite of passage.
怎么了
What?
感觉有东西舔了我一下
I think something just licked me.
我检查我们的钱包吧 这是你的
I'll just check our purses. Here's yours.
不用不用 我已经检查过了
Uh, no, no, no. I already checked that.
我的钱包里没东西...
There's nothing in mine...
只有一袋大麻
Except that baggie of pot
那是琦芙送我的圣诞礼物
that Keefer gave me as a Christmas present.
麦克斯 这不是什么圣诞礼物
Max, this is not a Christmas present.
这是满满一大袋的非法大麻
This is a giant, illegal, fat sack of weed.
对啊 可上面有个麋鹿贴纸
Yeah, with a Rudolph sticker,
所以这是圣诞礼物啦
which makes it a Christmas present.
看见没 他的红鼻子和红眼睛多喜庆
See? His nose and his eyes are red.
我不想看见这玩意 你得让它消失
I want this out of my sight. You gotta get rid of it.
我抽完这满满一袋
Well, it's gonna take me
至少得花45分钟呢
at least 45 minutes to smoke all that.
麦克斯 我是说真的
Max, I'm serious,
我看着这满满一袋大麻觉得很别扭
I'm not comfortable with that fat sack of weed.
别再用"满满一袋"这个词
Stop saying "fat sack of weed."
你就像那种学了潮流词就猛用的中年父亲
You're like someone's dad overusing the word "awesome."
我把它放上面吧
I'll just put it up here,
放在我留着新年嗑的半颗维柯丁[止痛药]旁边
next to the half a Vicodin I was saving for new year's.
别啊 我的大麻
Oh, no! The pot!
我的大麻掉进锅里了
The pot is in the pot!
掉到我要用来做小蛋糕的那锅黄油里了
It's in the butter I was using to make cupcakes.
也许这是老天爷的旨意
Maybe this is the universe's way
让你不要跟毒品沾边
of telling you to stop doing drugs.
或是在指引我们拿去卖掉
Or is it telling us to sell them?
麦克斯 我们没穷到那个地步
Max, we are not that desperate.
我们不用做大麻小蛋糕的
We're not making pot cupcakes.
我宁愿期待节日会带来什么惊喜
I'd rather just see what the holidays bring.
这里不是伯利恒 这里是布鲁克林
Well, this isn't Bethlehem, it's Brooklyn.
这里既没乳香 也无没药
There's no frankincense and myrrh,
这里只有"屌香"和"大麻药"
there's only frankenberry and "Myrrh-ajuana."
做出来结果很棒
These turned out great!
好主意 啊 老天爷
Good idea, universe.
我早就知道你也是麻友了
I knew you smoked weed.
天啊 这味道太难闻了吧
Oh, my God. I can't believe the smell.
像臭鼬被另一只臭鼬喷了臭气似地
It's like a skunk skunked a skunk.
我明白 就像狂欢会过后的
I know. It's like a port-a-potty
公共厕所一样臭
on the last day of Coachella.
惨了 栗宝在偷吸
Oh, no, Chestnut's smelling this.
我家小马都成毒虫了
I got my horse stoned.
别这么紧张
Oh, relax.
他只是想打入其他同学的圈子嘛
He's just trying to fit in at school.
你觉得邻居会闻到这味吗
Do you think the neighbors can smell it?
他们会不会打给警察举报我们啊
Do you think they're gonna call the cops?
别这么紧张啦
Chill out!
怎么有人还没能抽嗨 就这么多疑啊[副作用]
How can someone be this paranoid before they're high?
来 尝尝看
Here, taste this.
麦克斯 我才不碰大麻
Max, I don't do pot.
我大学的时候试过几次
I tried it a couple times in college.
会害我性格起大变化
It totally changed my personality.
那求你快吃了这大麻小蛋糕吧
Then please have some pot right now.
这是为了生意好吗
Come on, it's business.
得有人尝尝 告诉我味道如何啊
I need you to taste it and tell me how it is,
我现在尝不出来 做完这些
'cause I can't tell. At this point,
味道浓得我吃什么都会像大麻
everything I put in my mouth tastes like pot.
还不错呢
Hey, it's pretty good.
其实这味道蛮好吃的呢
In fact, it's kind of delicious.
我们应该收人家15块钱一个
We should charge 15 apiece for these.
这样能赚540块 刚好交租
That's $540. That's our rent.
你要是再多吃几口
A few more bites of that cupcake,
你就得多花两小时才算得出刚才的东西了
and that math would've taken two hours longer.
惨了 条子来了
Oh, my God! It's the cops!
估计就是上次那队特警
It's probably that same SWAT team!
我都说了让你别跟毒品沾边
I told you not to get involved with drugs!
我早告诉过你了
I told you!
闭嘴 卡洛琳 闭嘴
Shut it, Caroline! Shut it!
别紧张 是苏菲啦
Relax, it's Sophie.
姑娘们 我月经来了
Hi, girls. I got my period.
肚子疼得要死
Yeah, I got killer cramps.
像我子宫里有台拖拉机在乱搅一样
It's like I got a tractor in my uterus.
苏菲 你不舒服我们也很遗憾
Sophie, we're sorry you're not feeling well.
这种时候总让我觉得 老天爷真贱
Yeah, you know, it's times like these I think God's a bitch.
慢着 慢着
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
那是什么味道
What's that smell?
没什么 没什么味道
Nothing. It's nothing.
是大麻啊
Maui wowie!
你们这俩小姑娘还对我藏招啦
Oh, you girls have been holding out on me!
好啦 爽啊
Oh! All right! Okay!
老娘要的就是这个呀
This is what I'm talking about!
天啊 再见啦 疼死人的肚痛
Oh, my God, good-bye, killer cramps!
来吧 大麻派对
Hello, pot party!
老娘要来收成你们种下的"麻"了
I am picking up what you are laying down.
看来我们找到了我们新的产品代言人了
I think we found our new product spokesperson.
就是这里
Here it is.
我跟琦芙来过这里一次
I've been here once before with Keefer.
朱达是个很放松的人 有点电脑宅
Judah's a really chill guy, kind of a tech genius.
我们应该能把货全卖掉
Think we can probably sell them all here.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
整条路上你一句话都没说
You haven't spoken the entire way over here,
只可能是大麻的副作用
which is either a side effect of the pot,
或我提早收到了圣诞礼物
or my early Christmas present.
我没事啊 感觉跟以前一样
No, I'm fine. I feel exactly the same.
性格也完全没变化啊
It hasn't changed me at all.
小心盒子
Careful with the box,
小蛋糕会糊掉的
'cause you're smearing the cupcakes.
有啥关系 反正我们都会死
Oh, what does it matter? We're all gonna die.
这就是你跟我说的另一个人格吗
Is this that other personality you were telling me about?
我还是我啊 不过我屁都不是
No, it's still me. Not that I matter.
所有人都比屁还不如 都是要死的
None of us do. We're all gonna die.
惨了
Oh, crap.
麦克斯
Hey, Max!
接到你电话 我好高兴啊
I was so happy that you called.
你染上大麻无法自拔 我们也好高兴
And we're so happy you're addicted to marijuana.
抽大麻的人后来都会吸海洛因
You know it always leads to heroin--
之后就会死掉 我们都懂
Which leads to death. We get it.
你是唯一吸完毒还很无趣的人
You're the one not-fun stoner.
大伙们 卖零嘴的美女们来了
Hey, guys, the chicks are here with the edibles.
-零嘴 -我们在办小庆祝会
- Edibles! - We're having a little bit of a celebration.
我们卖大麻小蛋糕
Okay, so cupcakes.
15块一个 品质优良
They're 15 apiece, good quality.
大伙们 我们必须得全部卖掉 不然明天
And guys, we have to sell all of them, or tomorrow,
我们就得垃圾堆找东西吃了
we'll be eating out of a Dumpster.
有人有兴奋剂给她吃吗
Does anyone have any uppers?
我得去坐下了 生命啊
I have to sit down. I mean, life. Ugh!
我无力再假装一切都会好转了
I'm so tired of pretending it's all gonna be okay.
才不会呢
It's not.
你那个痣最好去检查一下吧
You should get that mole checked out.
我有不祥的预感
I don't feel good about it.
兄弟 这妞好吓人啊
Dude, this chick is freaking me out.
大卫 别紧张 我们买点吃的就好
Just take it easy, Dave. We'll just get some food in her.
我有个兄弟正带着披萨来呢
I got a buddy on the way with pizza.
兄弟们 我替她道歉
Guys, I'm sorry about her.
带她来 就像是带老妈去脱衣舞厅一样扫兴
It's like bringing your mother to a strip club.
我个人是无所谓 毕竟等于是载她去上班
Not for me. That'd be like taking my mom to work.
脱衣舞娘 想想她们的人生
Strippers, how about their lives?
一入欢场无尽期啊
They got no way out.
在你为有怪痣的脱衣舞娘唱曲之前
Can I talk to you, before you start performing
我能跟你借一步谈谈吗
an acoustic ballad about strippers with moles?
有啥好谈的啊 麦克斯
What's the point, Max?
扁吧 你要是要扁我 就扁吧
Go, if you're gonna hit me, hit me.
你是怎么了啊
What is happening with you?
原来白痴金发人群也会伤感的啊
I didn't even know blonde people could be sad.
麦克斯 我有话想对你说
Max, I have to tell you something.
靠近点 这是秘密 耳朵靠过来
Come here. It's a secret. Come here.
我们不会成功的
We're not gonna make it.
不都是你总在跟我说
But you're the one who's always telling me
一切都会好起来的吗
everything's gonna be fine.
对啊 都是我骗你的
Yeah, I was lying.
大麻在哪啊 你个小淫宅
Where's the weed, homeslizzy?
时间正好啊 安迪
Perfect timing, Andy.
这两姑娘是来卖零嘴的
These are the girls who are selling edibles.
不是啊 那是我女朋友 卡洛琳
No, that's my girlfriend, Caroline.
你真悲剧啊 兄弟
That sucks for you, dude.
你在这干嘛
What are you doing here?
她真是驾轻就熟啊
She is really getting the hang of that.
大概清晨四点左右
And around 4:00 A.M.,
你终于从松饼餐厅打来给我
you finally called me from an IHOP in Greenpoint,
然后我就去接你回来了
and I came and picked you up.
你当时满身沾了糖浆 大喊着
You were covered in syrup, yelling,
"玛雅人说得对 玛雅人说得对"
"The Mayans were right! The Mayans were right!"
我的小毒虫宝贝呀
There's my little stoner.
安迪 我才不是毒虫
Andy, I don't get stoned.
-我才不是毒虫 昨晚而已 -我知道
- It was just last night. - I know.
你半夜四点打给我时 都跟我说了
You told me all about it when you called at 4:00 A.M.
对不起啦 我还有件事不敢问
Sorry, and I'm mortified to ask,
但我是不是跟你电话性爱了
but did you and I have phone sex?
当时电话中的人是我
That was you and me.
毒虫卡洛琳很有市场啊
Stoned Caroline's got game.
麦克斯跟我说租金的事了
Hey, Max told me about the rent.
你为什么不跟我说你们需要帮忙呢
Why didn't you tell me you guys needed help?
我只是不想向你 或是对自己
I guess I just didn't want to have to admit
承认我们的店碰上了大麻烦
to you or to myself that we're in real trouble.
而且 从女朋友变成欠债人太不性感了
Plus, being a charity instead of a girlfriend is so not hot.
你无论做什么 都很难不性感
Uh, there is nothing you can do that is not hot.
那无论如何 你千万别看那
Oh, then whatever you do, do not look at the video
麦克斯拍我在松饼餐厅停车场打滚的影片
Max has of me, rolling around in the IHOP parking lot,
而且我还满身糖浆
covered in syrup.
我想你拿去
I want you to have this.
兑现 不兑现 都随你高兴
Cash it, don't cash it. Do whatever you want,
我只想你明白 我的成功如果不能与你同享
but just know that my success doesn't mean anything
那便一文不值
if I can't share it with you.
谢谢
Thank you.
安迪 你这么做我真的很感激
Andy, that is so amazing, and I really appreciate it,
但这钱我不能拿
but I can't take it.
好吧 这还算双赢
Well, it's a win-win.
至少拐到你把手放我裤子里了
At least it got your hand in my pants.
记住 你一有需要 它就在这里
And remember, if you ever need it, it's there.
我是说我的"大雕"
I'm talking about my penis.
安迪想给我们租金钱 我拒绝了
Andy offered to pay our rent, but I said no.
这真是我听过最蠢白人的事迹了
That is the whitest thing I've ever heard.
他这么做真的很有心
It was really sweet of him,
但我真的不想从我"睡的"男人那里拿钱
but I didn't want to take money from a man I'm sleeping with.
什么 你是说居然有女人
Wait, are you telling me there are women
不跟她"睡"的男人拿钱吗
who don't take money from men they're sleeping with?
接下来怎么办呢 麦克斯
What's gonna happen, Max?
我也不知道了
I don't know.
但我们有圣诞节装饰啊
But we do have Christmas decorations,
一起来摆上装饰吧
so let's put them up.
等等
Wait a minute.
居然是你在催我弄圣诞节
You're the one pushing Christmas?
你是谁啊 我吗
Who are you, me?
才不是你 我的尊严还在呢
No, I still have my dignity.
说到圣诞节 东方博士两个半来啦
Speaking of Christmas, here are the two and a half wise men.
-怎么啦 -卡洛琳昨晚打给我
- What's up? - Caroline called me last night.
说你们俩付不起租金
Told me that you two couldn't pay your rent,
你们会失去这小店
that you were losing the shop.
那妞话可多了哦
That girl can talk.
她也打给我了 说你们没钱交租
She called me too, and said you didn't have your rent,
她也说了 上升的海水会淹没全世界
and also that, for sure, the rising waters of the ocean
也会把所有人类统统淹死
will swallow us and kill us all.
我们就把身上的钱凑了凑 给
So we put together what we had, and... here.
就当是我们三个提前送的圣诞礼物吧
Consider it an early Christmas gift from all three of us...
虽然是我出了350 厄尔出了100
Even though I gave 350, Earl gave 100,
他只出了50块
and he gave 50.
谢谢你们 但我们不能收啊
Thank you, but we can't take it.
当然能收 我们是家人嘛
Yes, you can. We're family.
整整500块啊
500 whole dollars?
谢谢你们了
Thank you, guys.
我们也有特别的礼物送你们
And we have something special for you.
特别之处在哪啊
What makes it special?
她放里面的满满爱意啊
The love she puts into 'em, Max.
她满身都闻得到爱意呢
You can smell the love all around her.
麦克斯 我觉得我们会成功的
You know, Max, I think we're gonna make it.
我喜欢非毒虫版卡洛琳
I like not-stoned Caroline.
我们得让你离毒品远点才行
We're gonna keep you off the drugs.
因为我这时候比较乐观正面吗
You mean because I'm more positive?
是因为下个月的租进 可能得靠卖你的尿
No, 'cause we may have to sell your urine for next month's rent,
所以你绝对不能碰毒啊
and I'm gonna need that pee clean.